Ayush Chauhan

Frontend Developer

ABOUT ME

Hello, I am Ayush Chauhan, a front-end developer based in Noida. I have well versed experience in making Web Apps with React js, JavaScript. Our goal is to create captivating and user-friendly websites with seamless functionality and stunning design. I prioritize responsive design, ensuring your website looks great on all devices.

EXPERIENCE

Ui Cardio, Gurgaon— Frontend Developer (Intern)

Feb 2021 - June 2022

- → Worked with my senior developers to develop Bootstrap and Html 5 Templates.
- → I developed and manipulated themes for our clients with the guidance of my seniors in my team.

SFC Foundations, Chandigarh— Frontend Engineer

Sep 2021 - March2022

- → My primary responsibilities involved implementing changes to the event and blog sections of the website.
- → I was responsible for ensuring that the design and functionality of these sections were updated accurately and efficiently.

PROJECTS

• Portfolio Website - https://www.ayushchauhan.co.in/

This is my portfolio website. All my projects and services are mentioned there.

• Whats App Clone

-https://dulcet-sopapillas-ed5c60.netlify.app

(Under Development)

This clone is made in Reactjs, it uses UseState Context Api and Firebase for Backend and the messages.Router for switching chats in the chat box.

CONTACT INFO

- +91 9792757429
- +91 8707596169

webdeveloper.ayush@gmail.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- → JavaScript
- → React.js
- → Next js
- → Context Api
- → React Router
- → HTML5
- → CSS & SASS
- → Tailwind Css
- → React Redux
- → RESTful WebServices
- → Material Ui
 Components
- → Git (Version Control)
- → Responsive Web Design
- → Bootstrap
- → Landing Pages
- → Web Apps

EDUCATION

Asian Business School, Noida—(BCA)

July 2018 - April 2021

Social Profiles

Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/mrayush-chauhan/ Github https://github.com/webDevAyush